

# FERMIN CASILLAS

**Computer Systems Enginer** 

## **PROFILE**

Software Developer with focus on Web development. Experience programming in frameworks such as Angular, NestJS, and developing API services with GraphQL and much more.

As a person, I'm always trying to find the way to be a better Software Developer and improve my programming skills and learn new software trends. Another thought that I have is working as a team is one of the best things that people can do, because there are things that you don't learn alone and the support as team mates is worth.

If there is something that I don't know I can easily learn it from scratch. If there is an opportunity to be part of your company I will do my best to do a great work and I am always ready to face new challenges.

## **CONTACTS**

- ę
- +52 311-131-8186
- github.com/7Mica
- **♀** Tepic, NAY 63037

## **EDUCATION**

Instituto Tecnológico de Tepic Computer Systems Engineer Tepic, Nayarit 2012 • 2018

## LANGUAGES

Spanish (Native language)

English

## **HOBBIES**









## **EXPERIENCE**

2020 - Present

#### **Dot Devs**

Software Developer

- Worked designing and developing API services in NestJS Framwork and GraphQL
- Worked fixing issues for some Drupal Websites

2019 - 2020

#### D4ALL

Software Developer

- Worked developing Drupal Websites
- Worked developing Microsoft Umbraco Websites
- Worked doing QA for internal projects

2018 - 2019

#### **HETERIA GROUP**

Software Developer

- Designing and developing RESTful API services in Laravel
- Worked developing a human resources management system in Angular

2018 - 2018

#### ITT CIDETI

Software developer resident

- Wrote RESTful API services in Node.js (Express.js)
- Wrote single page applications with Angular
- Wrote mobile applications with IONIC

#### SKILLS

## **Programming Languages**

Typescript PHP Java SE

## **Frameworks**

Angular Express.js

NestJS Laravel

### **Others**

GraphQL Node.js

Drupal Sass

Docker \_\_\_\_